<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Tour Guide App</string>

    <string-array name="cities">
        <item>Calgary</item>
        <item>Toronto</item>
        <item>Edmonton</item>
        <item>Vancouver</item>
        <item>Quebec</item>
        <item>Victoria</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome to my tour guide app!!</string>
    <string name="Calgary">The physical setting of Calgary distinguishes it from other cities of the Prairie
        Provinces. It is situated on the western edge of the Great Plains, in the foothills of the
        spectacular Canadian Rockies (about 60 miles [100 km] to the west), and the surrounding
        valleys and uplands are a distinct change from the flat prairie landscapes typical of the
        region. A relatively young Canadian city, it is the administrative and financial
        headquarters of the country’s petroleum industry. Calgary also celebrates its history as a
        cattle-ranching capital, an image enhanced by the city’s hosting of the annual Calgary
        Stampede, a 10-day rodeo-centred event. In the early 21st century, Calgary was one of the
        fastest-growing cities in Canada.</string>
    <string name="Toronto">Canada’s most populous metropolitan area, it lies on the northern shore
        of Lake Ontario. Originally inhabited by Seneca tribes, its site was occupied by a tiny
        French fort in the mid-18th century. It was founded in 1793 as York by American colonists
        loyal to the British. U.S. troops pillaged it during the War of 1812. In 1834 it received
        its city charter and current name. It became the capital of Ontario in 1867. In 1953–54 it
        joined neighbouring villages, towns, and townships to form the Municipality of Metropolitan
        Toronto. In 1967 those 13 municipalities were reduced to six (Toronto, Etobicoke, North
        York, Scarborough, York, and the borough of East York), which amalgamated to form the City
        of Toronto in 1998. It is Canada’s financial and commercial centre, the seat of the Toronto
        Stock Exchange, and a major international trading centre, with access to Atlantic shipping
        via the Saint Lawrence Seaway and to major U.S. ports via the Great Lakes. It produces more
        than half of Canada’s manufactured goods. Extensive immigration (1950s–70s) brought a
        variety of foreign cultures that transformed it into one of the liveliest cities on the
        continent. It is the site of the CN Tower (1,815 ft [553 m] tall), the Hockey Hall of Fame,
        and the annual Canadian National Exhibition. Its educational institutions include the
        University of Toronto (1827).</string>
    <string name="Edmonton">Located on the North Saskatchewan River in the centre of the province,
        it began as a series of fur-trading posts built from 1795. With the arrival of the railway
        and an influx of settlers in the late 19th century, Edmonton began to prosper economically,
        and in 1905 it became the capital of the new province of Alberta. The 1947 discovery of
        petroleum in the area greatly stimulated the city’s growth; an agricultural and oil-based
        economy still prevails. It is the distribution centre of northwestern Canada. Its cultural
        and educational institutions include the University of Alberta (1906).</string>
    <string name="Vancouver">It is the major urban centre of western Canada and the focus of one of
        the country’s most populous metropolitan regions. Vancouver lies between Burrard Inlet (an
        arm of the Strait of Georgia) to the north and the Fraser River delta to the south,
        opposite Vancouver Island. The city is just north of the U.S. state of Washington. It has a
        fine natural harbour on a superb site facing the sea and mountains.</string>
    <string name="Quebec">It lies at the confluence of the St. Lawrence and St. Charles rivers,
        about 150 mi (240 km) northeast of Montreal, on a rocky promontory above the rivers.
        Canada’s oldest city, it was settled by the French in 1608 as a trading post. It was the
        capital of New France from 1663 to 1763, when it was lost to the British. It was the
        capital of Lower Canada 1791–1841 and Canada East 1841–67. It became the provincial capital
        in 1867. Most of the population is French speaking and Roman Catholic. It is the site of
        Laval University and other colleges and cultural institutions. Manufactures include
        newsprint, milled grain, cigarettes, and clothing. Shipbuilding and tourism are important
        industries.</string>
    <string name="Victoria"> It is located on the southeastern tip of Vancouver Island, overlooking
        Juan de Fuca Strait. It was founded in 1843 by the Hudson’s Bay Co. as a fur-trading post
        known as Fort Camosun; it was later renamed Fort Victoria to honour the English queen. It
        was selected as the capital in 1866 when Vancouver Island united with British Columbia. It
        is now one of the province’s largest business centres and a tourist resort and retirement
        community. A major port, it is the Pacific headquarters of the Canadian navy.</string>


</resources>